https://www.liequine.com/privacypolicy.php

04/24/2021IHA Dressage Clinic with 'Raul A. de Leon
liequine.com, a division of LI Horse Properties, is committed to protecting consumer privacy online. We believe that greater protection of personal privacy on the Web will not only protect consumers, but also increase consumer confidence and ultimately their participation in online activities. At liequine.com, we intend to give you as much control as possible over your personal information.
The purpose of our policy is to inform you about the types of information we gather about you when you visit our site(s), how we may use that information, whether we disclose it to anyone, and the choices you have regarding our use of, and your ability to correct, the information.
Our site(s) may contain links to other Web sites, including Web sites directed to children. We have no control over the privacy practices or the content of any of our business partners, advertisers, sponsors or other sites to which we provide links from our sites. You should check the applicable privacy policy of the Web site sponsor when linking to other Web sites.
I. Information Which We Collect
We may request that you voluntarily supply us with personal information, including your e-mail address, postal address, home or work telephone number, credit card number (only if you choose to purchase a product online), for purposes such as correspondence, making a purchase, or participating in online contests, surveys or games. If you choose to give us personal information via the Internet that we or our business partners may need -- to correspond with you, process an order or provide you with a subscription, for example -- it is our intent to let you know how we will use such information.
Like many other commercial sites, our site(s) may utilize a standard technology called a "cookie" to collect information about how our site is used. Cookies were designed to help a Web site recognize a user's browser as a previous visitor and thus save and remember any preferences that may have been set while the user was browsing the site. A cookie cannot retrieve any other data from your hard drive, pass on a computer virus, or capture your e-mail address. Our Web site(s) may use cookies to enhance your visit. Cookies can securely store a user's password, personalize home pages, identify which parts of a site have been visited or keep track of selections, such as those selected in a "shopping cart." Our cookies may collect your domain name and track your selections through our Web pages. We only use "cookies" to gather the information indicated in this policy and do not use cookies to gather personal identifying information about you without your consent.
We also may use cookies in connection with our chat rooms in order to record your preferences. These cookies store automatically information pertaining to the last chat room you visited, as well as certain comments that can be issues in the chat room, in order to facilitate your experience with the chat rooms. No additional identifying information is stored on these cookies. You also have the option of choosing to allow us to use a cookie to store your username, or "handle" and password on your computer for use in that chat rooms, forums and other sites as indicated on the particular site.
We may require you to supply us with personal information (demographic information such as average age, income, education, population data, zip codes) during a "registration" process online prior to using certain features of our site. For example, you may be required to register to use chat rooms, forums, to access archival stories, to subscribe to our member newspapers, subscribe to an e-mail version of our site, and to access other features. We use this general information to aggregate information according to demographics, such as gender, geographic location, age, income or a combination of these or other demographics.
II. Use of User Information
We may perform statistical analyses of aggregate user behavior. This allows us to measure relative consumer interest in the various areas of our Web sites for product development purposes. Any information we collect is used for its own internal purposes to improve the content of the Web sites, to enhance users' experiences when visiting our site(s), to customize the content and/or layout of our pages, and to provide the services required by an individual user. We do not use personal identifying information for any reason that is not disclosed either in this Policy or at the time the information is requested. We never send e-mail to you unless you request a particular service, or consent to being contacted by e-mail. There are instances where you will have the opportunity to subscribe to an e-mail list that will send information about the site or our advertisers to your e-mail address, but this will be done only with your permission and consent
III. Disclosure to Third Parties
We do not share personal identifying information with any third party without your permission. We disclose only in aggregate form our statistical analyses or demographics of users to third parties, such as advertisers or other business partners. In some instances, we operate shared Web sites with businesses affiliated with us. Our privacy policy will apply to these Web sites, and our affiliates adhere to our privacy policy and will not share personal information with any third party without your permission. PLEASE BE AWARE that when you voluntarily disclose personal information (such as your name, e-mail address) in chat areas or bulletin boards to third parties, that information may be collected by others outside the control of us and may result in unsolicited messages from others.
IV. Accuracy of User Information
In order to ensure the accuracy of personal information provided for registration, you may return to the registration form online in order to change information you have provided at any time. Questions regarding our privacy policy, the accuracy of your personal information or the use of the information collected should be directed via e-mail to James Cotgreave, or you can reach us by telephone at 631-979-2965. You can also write us at:
Long Island Horse Properties
2150 Joshua's Path
Hauppauge, NY 11788
These privacy policies are effective as of Dec. 1, 2001. We reserve the right to change this policy at any time, and will post any changes to this policy as soon as they go into effect.
V. Security of Information
We use our best efforts to ensure the security of personal information submitted by users. When collecting credit card information for online purchases, we offer secured-server transactions that encrypt your information in transit to thwart someone from intercepting it and misusing it. When we collect other information from our users, it is stored in an area where the general public does not have access to it.
VI. Opting-out
At any time while accessing our site(s), any user while online may "opt-out" of further e-mail contact from us (while still allowing access to our site(s)). For further information about opting-out, contact us at the e-mail addresses, postal addresses or telephone numbers stated above. You can opt-out of any future mailings by sending an email FROM YOUR EMAIL ADDRESS to unsubscribe@lihorseproperties.com
VII. Use of Materials
The right to download and store or output the materials in our site(s) is granted for the user's personal use only, and materials may not be reproduced in any edited form. Any other reproduction, transmission, performance, display or editing of these materials by any means mechanical or electronic without the express written permission of us is strictly prohibited. Users wishing to obtain permission to reprint or reproduce any materials appearing on these sites may contact us at privacy@liequine.com.
Long Island Equine, 19 West Main St. Smithtown, NY 11787.
Phone:
(631) 979-2965
email:
office@lihorseproperties.com
STAY UPDATED ON
ALL THINGS HORSES
AND EQUINE PROPERTIES
Largest source for equine properties in Long Island, New York
